var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَتَاكَ",
        "answer": "(there) come to you",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "atāka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآثَرَ",
        "answer": "And preferred",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waāthara",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَهُ",
        "answer": "So seized him",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhahu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(for) the last",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَإِذَا",
        "answer": "What! When",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "a-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "And the earth",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "552",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2825",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "726",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "727",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "728",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "To",
        "pcklId": "729",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرًا",
        "answer": "(the) matter",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "amran",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the first",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wal-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَأْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) the refuge",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-mawā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَأْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "the refuge",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-mawā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَةَ",
        "answer": "the sign",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "l-āyata",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبُرِّزَتِ",
        "answer": "And will be made manifest",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waburrizati",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَارُهَا",
        "answer": "Their eyes",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "abṣāruhā",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنَاهَا",
        "answer": "He constructed it",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "banāhā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْبَعُهَا",
        "answer": "Follows it",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tatbaʿuhā",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِبَالَ",
        "answer": "And the mountains",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wal-jibāla",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمَ",
        "answer": "the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīma",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "Paradise ",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتِ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "jāati",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدِيثُ",
        "answer": "(the) story",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ḥadīthu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحَشَرَ",
        "answer": "And he gathered",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "faḥashara",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَافِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the former state",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ḥāfirati",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةَ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayata",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "and brought out",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "wa-akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "He brought forth",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "losing",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "khāsiratun",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاشِعَةٌ",
        "answer": "humbled",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khāshiʿatun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "so you would fear",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "fatakhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "fears",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yakhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَاهَا",
        "answer": "fears it",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yakhshāhā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقًا",
        "answer": "creation",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "khalqan",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَافَ",
        "answer": "feared",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "khāfa",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْبَرَ",
        "answer": "he turned his back",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "adbara",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْمُدَبِّرَاتِ",
        "answer": "And those who arrange",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "fal-mudabirāti",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَحَاهَا",
        "answer": "He spread it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "daḥāhā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُ",
        "answer": "will remember",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkaru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرَاهَا",
        "answer": "(to) mention it",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "dhik'rāhā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْهَبْ",
        "answer": "Go",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "idh'hab",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرَاهُ",
        "answer": "Then he showed him",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "fa-arāhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "sees",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "yarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَهَا",
        "answer": "they see it",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "yarawnahā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "930",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "931",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمُ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "932",
        "tlit": "rabbukumu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "(before) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "933",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "934",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْجُفُ",
        "answer": "will quake",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tarjufu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّاجِفَةُ",
        "answer": "the quaking one",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-rājifatu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَرْدُودُونَ",
        "answer": "indeed be returned",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "lamardūdūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّادِفَةُ",
        "answer": "the subsequent",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-rādifatu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَاهَا",
        "answer": "He made them firm",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "arsāhā",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرْسَاهَا",
        "answer": "(is) its arrival",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "mur'sāhā",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَرْعَاهَا",
        "answer": "and its pasture",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wamarʿāhā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَفَعَ",
        "answer": "He raised",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "rafaʿa",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَجْرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a shout",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "zajratun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزَكَّىٰ",
        "answer": "purify yourself",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tazakkā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْحًا",
        "answer": "swimming",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "sabḥan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّابِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "And those who glide",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wal-sābiḥāti",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْقًا",
        "answer": "(in) a race",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "sabqan",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالسَّابِقَاتِ",
        "answer": "And those who race each other",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "fal-sābiqāti",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "striving",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعَىٰ",
        "answer": "he strove (for)",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "saʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمْكَهَا",
        "answer": "its ceiling",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "samkahā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّاهِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(will be) awakened",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-sāhirati",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "answer": "and proportioned it",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fasawwāhā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "a more difficult",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُحَاهَا",
        "answer": "its brightness",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḍuḥāhā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُحَاهَا",
        "answer": "a morning thereof",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḍuḥāhā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَىٰ",
        "answer": "(has) transgressed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṭaghā",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَىٰ",
        "answer": "transgressed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ṭaghā",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّامَّةُ",
        "answer": "the Overwhelming Calamity",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ṭāmatu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُوًى",
        "answer": "(of) Tuwa",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭuwan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعِبْرَةً",
        "answer": "surely (is) a lesson",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "laʿib'ratan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشِيَّةً",
        "answer": "an evening",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ʿashiyyatan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَصَىٰ",
        "answer": "and disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "waʿaṣā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِظَامًا",
        "answer": "bones",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "ʿiẓāman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Most High",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-aʿlā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَرْقًا",
        "answer": "violently",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "gharqan",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَغْطَشَ",
        "answer": "And He darkened",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-aghṭasha",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَدَّسِ",
        "answer": "the sacred",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-muqadasi",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبٌ",
        "answer": "Hearts",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "qulūbun",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "1601",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "1602",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "1603",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "Then he said",
        "pcklId": "1604",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَامَ",
        "answer": "standing",
        "pcklId": "582",
        "tlit": "maqāma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُبْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-kub'rā",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُبْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-kub'rā",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "But he denied",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "fakadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(would be) a return",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "karratun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we are",
        "pcklId": "1344",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْبَثُوا",
        "answer": "they had remained",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yalbathū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْلَهَا",
        "answer": "its night",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "laylahā",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "(As) a provision",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "matāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءَهَا",
        "answer": "its water",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "māahā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخِرَةً",
        "answer": "decayed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nakhiratan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَاهُ",
        "answer": "called him",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "nādāhu",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "and called out",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "fanādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْذِرُ",
        "answer": "(are) a warner",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "mundhiru",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّازِعَاتِ",
        "answer": "By those who extract",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wal-nāziʿāti",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشْطًا",
        "answer": "gently",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nashṭan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّاشِطَاتِ",
        "answer": "And those who draw out",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-nāshiṭāti",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِأَنْعَامِكُمْ",
        "answer": "and for your cattle",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "wali-anʿāmikum",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّفْسَ",
        "answer": "his soul",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "l-nafsa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكَالَ",
        "answer": "(with) an exemplary punishment",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nakāla",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَهَى",
        "answer": "and restrained",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wanahā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْتَهَاهَا",
        "answer": "(is) its finality",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "muntahāhā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْدِيَكَ",
        "answer": "And I will guide you",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "wa-ahdiyaka",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "the vain desires",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-hawā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاجِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "will palpitate",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wājifatun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْوَادِ",
        "answer": "in the valley",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bil-wādi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "79",
        "ayah": "46"
    }
]; 
export default words;